

## YOVIE ALFAGUISTUTA

## Web Developer

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am 24 years old and I am a web developer who have 2+ years of experience. Coding on React JS, Laravel and Go Language. I Already serve several clients to build web based applications. My greatest strength in technical terms is problem solving and logical thinking. I am also very enthusiastic and interested to use or learn new things.

#### SOFT SKILL

- Problem Solving
- Logical Thinking
- Creativty
- Time Management
- Teamwork

#### TECH STACK

- React JS (Typescript)
- Next JS (Typescript)
- Laravel
- Golang

## PROGRAMMING TOOLS

- Git
- Redux
- Redux Saga
- Docker & PM2
- Go Fiber
- Postman
- Swagger

# **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2021

Bachelor degree S1 Informatika (S.Kom) at Universitas Teknokrat Indonesia,

GPA 3,45.

2015 - 2017

High school graduate from SMAN 5 Bandar Lampung, Science Major

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Web Developer Microdata Indonesia 2020 - Present

Placed on the Frontend or Backend. Develop multiple applications ranging from government, large enterprises and small businesses with industry standard technology. Most applications are built with React and Laravel. Usually use Golang if the project time is long enough.

Web Developer Freelance 2020 - 2022

Jest & Cypress

Jira & Trello

PostgreeSql

Linux

CI CD

Freelancers who are not tied to any companies (External project). The projects such as from UMKM, college assignments and even theses. Applications made such as E-Learning, Payment, Intern Management and others. Everything is made and designed by myself from the beginning to the application until the app ready to launch

Internship Android Developer BAPPEDA (Intern) Internship for 2 month. Develop 2 Android Mobile Apllication:

- RPJMD
- · UPD

2020

### LANGUAGE

Indonesia

English



**Email** 

yoviealfaguistuta@gmail.com



Address

Pulau Sanama Street, Bandar Lampung



https://yoviealfaguistuta.site

